## Justinas Baskys, Software Developer

justinas.baskys@gmail.com

in Justinas Baškys

📍 Šiauliai, Lithuania

Having recently obtained a Bsc Honours degree in Computer Game Development, I am looking for a team that I can infuse with my knowledge, passion and love for games. After living in the UK for 10 years, I've mastered the language and overcome quite a few challenges, now it's time to find the ideal company to work for and grow my skillset. During my time at university I've gained experience working in a team effectively, planning & managing deadlines, methodologies, version control, testing and working with various tools to implement mechanics, animation & assets as well as anything else that might need to be created on the go - for this reason I can offer a decent amount of versatility for any team. More recently I've been leaning into full-stack development with my main tools being React, Next.js, JavaScript, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS and so far I've been really enjoying great results and could definitely see myself as a full-stack developer.

## **Education**

University of Westminster - BSc (Hons) Computer Games Development, 2019-2023.

During my time at westminster I was a hard-working student and really enjoyed the content we were taught which included all stages of the game development lifecycle with a focus on programming & technical knowledge of industry standard software. My specialty became C# and Unity, having also worked on projects using Unreal Engine 4 (Blueprints), C++, Monogame Pipeline, SwiftUI (iOS), web development using HTML, CSS & JavaScript. I also have experience working with Maya, 3DS Max, Aseprite (2D) and Photoshop. I learned a vast amount of theory & created functionality relating for game design, methodologies, graphics programming, AI & pathfinding, Physics & other algorithm implementation, networking for games, business analysis & many more.

**Evesham College** - Level 3 IT Extended Diploma and Level 3 Creative Media Production 90 Credit Diploma, 2016-2019

During the IT course I gained a vast amount of entry knowledge in programming & theory about computers, networks as well as developing simple websites and applications using Java, Visual Basic, PHP & SQL and HMTL & CSS. During the Creative Media Production course designed games, drawn art, created assets & animation using Maya and worked on a couple of projects including using Unreal Engine 4.

## **Work Experience**

**Pers Hotell/Casa Nostra** - Waiter/bartender in a hotel restaurant & bar in Norway 06/2023-09/2023 Full-time;

**IDL** - Steel-fixer/construction worker at multiple locations in London 05/2022-09/2022 Full-time;

**Day & Night** - Kitchen Porter in a busy restaurant in London 06/2021-10/2021 Full-time;